I can't go home today.
もう帰れないよ、今日
good?
いい?
Here, spread your legs for now.
ほら、足開いてとりあえず
Open it, open it.
開いてごらん、開いてごらん
It won't end.
終わらないよ
It never ends, you see.
終わらないって、ほら
Spread your legs properly and see.
足開いてちゃんと、ほら
Yeah, it's okay.
うん、大丈夫
It's okay, nothing.
大丈夫だよ、別に
I have to check it out now.
もう、チェックしないと
There it is, so open your legs.
あるから、足開いて
Oh yeah, yeah.
そうそう、そう
It won't end if I don't do it.
もう、しないと終わんないから
copper?
どう?
here?
ここ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
copper?
どう?
Don't you feel?
気持ちくない?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
what up?
どうした?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫だよ、大丈夫だよ
It's not over, you know.
終わらないよ、ほら
You understand, right?
分かるでしょ?
Because there is something like this.
こういうのあるから
There is something like this.
こういうのあるんだよ
Not particularly evil
別に悪
It's not that bad.
く ないよ
It's not bad at all.
別 に悪くないよ
Want to cry more comfortably?
もっと気持ちよく泣いたい?
Hey, hey, I'll take it outside.
ちょ、ちょ、外に出すから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's crazy, I can't stand it.
やばい、ちょっと我慢できない
terrible.
やばい
You haven't put it out, have you?
出してないでしょ?
Here, turn around and look.
こっち、後ろ向いて、ほら
Stick one out.
一枚突き出して
There's no choice but to do it, right?
やらしかないでしょ?
Just like that.
そんまに
Stick it out more towards your hips and see.
腰へもっと突き出して、ほら
You can do it.
できるんだ
By yourself.
自分で
Can you move by yourself?
自分で動けるの?
Alright then, stop.
じゃあいいよ、足止めて
Stop.
足 止めて
足止めて
Take it out slowly.
ゆっくり出して
Yeah, isn't it amazing?
うん、すごいしょ?